{
    "subject": "resource/St._Stanislaus_Institute_(Slovenia)",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Slovenia",
    "human_readable": "St. Stanislaus Institute (Slovenia) is located in Slovenia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.922231137752533,
            "question": "Where is St. Stanislaus Institute located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8798820376396179,
            "question": "In what country is St. Stanislaus Institute situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7680185437202454,
            "question": "What type of institution is St. Stanislaus Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7103427648544312,
            "question": "Is there a website for St. Stanislaus Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565888524055481,
            "question": "Is St. Stanislaus Institute in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6120173335075378,
            "question": "What is the history of St. Stanislaus Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5951482057571411,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about St. Stanislaus Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5004308819770813,
            "question": "Does St. Stanislaus Institute offer a range of academic programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4758775234222412,
            "question": "Are there any famous alumni from St. Stanislaus Institute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1988595724105835,
            "question": "What is the name of the institution?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=St. Stanislaus Institute (Slovenia) is located in Slovenia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7457_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous alumni from St. Stanislaus Institute?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7457_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does St. Stanislaus Institute offer a range of academic programs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7457_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about St. Stanislaus Institute?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7457_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7457_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about St. Stanislaus Institute (Slovenia), which includes its location, educational institution type, and other details. Specifically, it states that the institute is a Slovenian Roman Catholic educational institution in \u0160entvid, Ljubljana, Slovenia. This confirms that the institute is indeed located in Slovenia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the St. Stanislaus Institute, which is based in Ljubljana, Slovenia. This supports the statement that the institute is located in Slovenia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}